# Komlan ZANKPE

# **DevOps Engineer**

Skilled Devops Engineer with strong experience on **Azure cloud**. Used several technologies to monitor 200+ Windows Servers. At Neocase Software, effectively led the **automation** works in the team. Built pipelines with **PowerShell** and Azure Devops tools to reduce release time by 50%. Proficient with **Infrastructure** as **Code** and configuration management.

# **Work History**

# 2018-11 - present

# Cloud Devops Engineer

Neocase Software, La Garenne Colombes (FRANCE)

A leading provider of integrated HR and Finance service delivery solutions At the core of Cloud and Security team, leading the automation work to cut down delivery time:

- · Deployed applications to Azure cloud
- Created PowerShell scripts to automate deployments
- ARM template and DSC used to build Infrastructure as Code
- Monitored client's application with ELK stack
- Developed **custom PowerShell module** for application administration
- Analytical thinking to resolve critical issues encountered in production

### 2016-06

- 2018-10

### **Technical Implementation Manager**

Ariane Systems, Pantin (FRANCE)

A company providing online check-in/out technologies to the hotel industry. Within the project team and collaborating with the development team:

- PaaS management: deployment and management of azure resources
- · Connection of client applications through webservices
- · Advanced technical support on the applications
- · Wrote training documentation and guidelines

# 2014-02

- 2016-03

### **Field Service Engineer**

Arelis Group, Colombes (FRANCE)

Specialized in design and integration of electronic solutions

Working with the 2nd Authority for Television and Radio (Jerusalem). Broadcasting DVBT and DVBT2 signal in Israel:

- Installation and maintenance of RF transmitters
- · Network monitoring
- · Storage and resources management
- Ensure client's expectations were satisfied

### **Education**

# 2009-09

- 2012-09

#### Institut Supérieur d'Electronique de Paris, FRANCE

Master's Degree, Telecommunication Engineering

Classes: Signal processing, Wireless networks, Electronics, Digital communications, Web development ...

#### **Certificates**

**Az-104: Microsoft Azure Administrator** 

Az-400: Designing and Implementing Microsoft DevOps Solutions

# **Personal Info**

#### **Email**

kzankpe@gmail.com

#### **Phone**

+33(0)695294930

#### **Skype**

kzankpe

#### **Address**

66 rue d'estienne d'orves 93110 Rosny sous bois FRANCE

## **Soft Skills**

Agile Methodology

Critical Thinking

Teamwork

Continuous Improvement

# **Technical Skills**

Cloud Management (Azure)

Configuration Management

CI/CD (Azure Devops)

Version Control Software (Git)

**ARM Template** 

Terraform

Powershell

Python

Windows server

IIS

MS SQL Server

Kubernetes

Unix/Linux

# Languages

French



English